你的烤起司三明治
Here's your grilled cheese.
切边了
No crust.
太好了
Cool.
能麻烦你把填色的东西移开吗 先生
And can you just move your coloring materials, sir?
你看
Look.
"真好看"
Pretty.
我出生在经济大萧条时期
I was born during the Great Depression,
但我还没看过比
and I never saw anything as depressing
那个都他妈多少岁了的白人男娃
as that grown-ass white boy
在画填色本更悲哀[萧条]的事了
coloring in the damn coloring book.
我出生在威豹乐队演唱会上
I was born during a Def Leppard concert...
而那是我这辈子看过最悲哀的事了
And that is the most depressing thing I've ever seen.
我要过去教育教育他
I'm gonna go school him.
或者应该说是 学前教育他
Or, in his case, pre-school him.
麦克斯 别太狠
Max, be gentle.
他正处于他的悲惨32岁时期
I think he's in the middle of his terrible 32s.
打扰了 巴拉巴拉红黄蓝
Excuse me, OshKosh B'gosh.
我对你的填色本有个问题
I have a question about your coloring book.
你干毛呢
Why?
这是成人着色本
Oh, they're for adults.
超有禅意
Super Zen.
超能让人沉思
Super meditative.
还有助于解压
Helps with stress.
你知道还有什么事能有助于解压吗
You know what else helps with stress?
做爱
Sex.
就算某个攻能忍受
And even if someone could get past
你那看了就让人阳痿的吊带裤
those boner-killing overalls...
但如果你继续涂涂涂 你这辈子也别想啪啪啪
you ain't gonna have any of that if you keep this up.
更不用说 你生活能有什么压力啊
Not to mention, how stressful can your life really be
你都有空在周二下午三点
if you are carefully shading a unicorn's ass
为独角兽的菊花仔细描阴影
3:00 P.M. on a Tuesday?
上菜 蔬菜卷
Pickup. Veggie wrap.
我勒个去 他在打炮
Oh, my God, he's having sex.
卡洛琳 你装什么假正经
Oh, Caroline, don't be such a prude.
太好了 是苏菲
Oh, good, it's Sophie.
我还担心他又开始插那个贝果
I was worried he was at that bagel again.
是谁说怀孕的女人就不能
Who says that a pregnant woman can't have sex
在餐厅厨房地上做爱呢
on the kitchen floor of a diner?
卫生部的人 苏菲
The Health Department, Sophie.
做完爱好口渴啊
Oh boy, sex makes me thirsty.
她就直接无视那些杯子
She just blew right past those cups.
苏菲 在你怀孕的时候跟你做爱
Sophie, having sex with you pregnant
比跟你得禽流感的时候做爱还带劲
is even hotter than having sex when you had the bird flu.
是啊 我一样全身冒汗
Yeah, well, you know, I'm just as sweaty,
但是不怎么打喷嚏
but I sneeze less.
苏菲 怀孕真是丝毫没有
Sophie, you're really not letting
妨碍你做爱的频率
this pregnancy slow you down.
你光是今天打过的炮
You've already had more sex just today
就比卡洛琳一年的量还多
than Caroline's had all year.
而且你都没穿孕妇装
You're not even in maternity clothes.
对啊
Yeah.
我才不需要穿那种单调像土豆麻袋的衣服
Well, I don't need to wear one of those frumpy potato sacks.
因为我可是性感土豆姐
Yeah, because I'm a hot potato!
厄尔你看什么呢
Earl, what are you looking at?
我也不知道我看到什么鬼
I have no idea.
好了 麦克斯
All right, Max...
是时候来聊聊那件你不想聊的事
It's time to have that uncomfortable conversation again.
好吧 但我记得是你自己说
Okay, but I thought you said it was a hard no
打死不在谈话节目的背景窗前做爱
on having sex in front of the Today Show window?
来嘛
Oh, come on.
我来这里的期限就要到了
My month here is almost up.
我得回洛城了 我们需要个计划
I have to get back to L.A., and we need a plan.
我们有计划啊
We have a plan.
我用着大衣卖场里捡到的节育环来"计划"生育
I use the NuvaRing I found at the Burlington Coat Factory.
那里真的不是只有好大衣而已哦
They really are more than great coats.
麦克斯 说点现实的
Max, let's get real.
麦克斯不喜欢谈论现实
Max doesn't like to talk about reality
除非是真人[现实]秀
unless it's reality TV.
就像她上过的那集警察抓犯人真人秀
Like the Cops New Orleans episode she was on.
那是那家电视台首次播出过奶头呢
It's the only time Fox has ever aired a nipple.
谁点了韩国男团啊
Uh, who ordered the Korean boy band?
请问有事吗
Uh, can I help you?
你好
Yeah, hi.
我来找李憨
I'm looking for Han Lee.
身高到这里
'Bout yay big.
蠢度到这里
'Bout yay stupid.
你想找阿憨吗
You're looking for Han?
是光阿憨 还是想要搜集整套阿憨迷你娃
Just Han, or are you trying to collect the whole set?
你长得像一个叫"棒"的韩国明星
You kind of look like this Korean pop star named Bong.
我的大麻烟斗[棒]也是韩国做的呢
Well, my bong is from Korea.
阿憨不在
Uh, Han is not here.
如果你见到他
Well, if you see him,
告诉他黄哥来找过他
just tell him Hwang came to say,
如果他不回我电话 他就要三好球[出局]
if he doesn't call me back, he's got three strikes
而且没坏球[蛋蛋]
and no balls.
他知道
Oh, he knows that.
天啊 你觉得阿憨是不是惹上什么麻烦了
Oh, my God, do you think Han may be in some sort of trouble?
我好担心
I'm really worried.
有个牌子要打折了
Oh, J. Crew sale!
等我们付完刷墙工 电工 管道工的钱
So, after we pay the painters, the electrician, the plumber,
当然还有贿赂检查员后
and, of course, the bribes to the inspectors,
我们刚好有足够钱可以拿来当
we have just enough money left for what I like to call
"保底救急金"
a little "cash cush."
如果是买大麻的救急金 我超欢迎
If that's cash we use for kush, I'm excited about it.
这钱不能乱花 假装它不存在吧
We can't spend that money, so pretend it's not there,
就像你眼里的可回收垃圾桶一样
like you do with recycling bins.
惨了
Oh, no!
老鼠又把防水布里当角斗场了
The rats are using our tarp as their Superdome again!
我拿砸鼠锤
I'll get the rat mallet!
拜托别拿砸鼠锤
No, don't get the rat mallet!
是会说话的耗子 快去拿枪
It's a talking one, get the gun.
哎哟 这不是"卧鼠藏笼"的男主角吗
Well, if it isn't Crouching Loser, Hidden Virgin.
姑娘们 我现在正处于水深火热中
Girls, I'm in a bit of hot water.
怎么了 你又不小心掉进茶杯里了吗
What happened, you fell into a tea cup again?
不是 我深陷困境
No, I'm in deep trouble!
你这辈子才没"深入"过任何地方
You've never been in deep anything.
等等 是因为这样所以那些牛鬼蛇神
Well, wait, is that why those scary-looking guys
才跑来餐厅找你
came into the diner looking for you
然后说出那些狠话吗
and made some threats?
好像是跟什么出局无蛋蛋有关吧
I remember something about a strike and no balls.
好像跟无蛋蛋有关吧
Something about no balls?
你们俩恶女居然连威胁我性命的话
You monsters didn't get the precise wording
都没有听好记牢吗
on a threat to my life?
我当时有些分心嘛 阿憨
I was a little distracted, Han.
有个牌子声称要打五折
J. Crew claimed to have a 50% off sale,
结果我点进去 发现是"最高五折"
but then I clicked on the link, and it was an "Up to" 50% sale.
大部分都是男性西装
Mostly on men's suiting.
麻烦你把链接发给我
Oh, do send me the link
我好选入葬时穿的寿衣
so I can select the suit I'll be buried in!
因为你们俩连个留言都记不好
Because you two can't take a damn message!
好了 阿憨 到底怎么回事
All right, Han, what is going on?
你真的惹了麻烦吗
Are you really in trouble?
刚才是什么声音
What was that?
帮帮我 高大强壮的猛男
Help me, strong, big man!
刚才不是枪声 阿憨
That wasn't gunshots, Han,
只是有车引擎逆火了
it was just a car backfiring.
到底怎么啦
What's going on?
这件事情不好启齿
Well, there's no easy way to say it.
我有严重的赌瘾
I have a pretty substantial gambling problem.
阿憨 没想到你还挺会玩
But Han, that's almost interesting.
我也挺快要入土了
Yeah, and I'm almost history!
为免你没听懂
In case you weren't following,
我欠了一屁股债
I'm in a lot of debt!
小兄弟 有我在呢
Han, my man, I'm here for you.
跟我们说吧
Tell us what it is.
扑克 赌马还是赌球
Poker, ponies, football?
是...
It's...
赌女子网球
ladies tennis.
女子网球吗
Ladies tennis?
我都不知道你还打网球
I didn't even know you played tennis.
这运动可魔性了
Yeah, well, it's a vicious sport.
我的钱都输在那对威廉姆斯姐妹身上了
And I lost most of my money on those Williams sisters.
就像歌词唱得 "不要相信微笑的大屁股妞"
Never trust a big butt and a smile.
还用你说
You're telling me!
是我看走眼 错把草当宝押
I thought the bad one was the good one.
你欠这些人多少赌债
How much do you owe these people?
一开始欠的债加上利息
Well, with the initial debt and the interest.
我欠的债大概是...
I'm told it's in the neighborhood
一个黑市肾的价格吧
of a black market kidney.
那些肾可不便宜呢
Those are pretty pricey.
我知道就是因为我身上有两个
I know, I have two of them.
阿憨 故事引人入胜
Han, that's fascinating,
又令人不寒而栗
yet disturbing.
就像在便宜炮房用黑光灯照体液一样可怕
Like when you use a black light at a Red Roof Inn.
你就像个米团
You're like an enigma.
拜托 是谜团好吗
Enigma, please.
阿憨 这个黄哥能凶到哪儿去啊
Han, how dangerous can Hwang be?
他的办公处在K房里
His office is in a karaoke bar.
他唯一会谋杀[糟蹋]的是
The only thing he's gonna murder
是霍尔与奥兹二重唱的歌单
is the Hall and Oates catalogue.
阿憨 你得面对这个恶霸
Han, you have to face this bully.
这是你人生中最大的恶霸给你的建议
And this is coming from your biggest bully.
听话 按我说的做 不然就揍你
Now come on, do what I say, or I'll beat you up.
走起
Here we go.
我突然想起来 我得拿一下毛衣
Oh, I just remembered... I need to get my sweater.
家里那件
From my home.
韩国的家
In Korea.
♪ 这是我们初次见面 ♪
♪ Hey I just met you ♪
Call me maybe - Carley Rae Japsen
♪ 我也知道这样很疯狂 ♪
♪ And this is crazy ♪
♪ 但这是我的电话号码 ♪
♪ So here's my number ♪
♪ 有机会要打给我哦 ♪
♪ so call me maybe ♪
♪ 而其他的小妞们呢 ♪
♪ And all the other girls ♪
♪ 也都想倒追我 ♪
♪ Try to chase me ♪
♪ 但这是我的电话号码 ♪
♪ But here's my number ♪
♪ 有机会要打给我哦 ♪
♪ So call me maybe ♪
他好像很忙
He looks busy.
九月再来找他吧
Let's revisit this in September.
好像来了客人呢
Oh, I see we have company.
进来 坐下 把我的钱交出来
Come in, sit down, give me my money.
黄先生听我说
Look, Mr. Hwang.
我们知道阿憨对白色百褶短裙
We understand Han has a weakness for pleated white skirts
与粗壮大腿没有抵抗力
and over-developed thighs.
坐下 我来处理
Slow down, let me handle this.
我有丰富跟江湖惯犯的交手经验
I have experience with hardened criminals.
首先 那女歌手的歌你唱太赞了
First off, killer Carly Rae Jeps.
你介意我先自罚个五杯烈酒吗
Um, do you mind if a sister does, like, five shots?
听我说 黄先生
Look, Mr. Hwang.
居然敢直呼我的名字 "黄"
Call me by my first name: Hwang.
你的姓名叫黄·黄吗
Your names is Hwang Hwang?
你觉得很好笑吗
Oh, you think that's funny?
阿金也觉得好笑
So did Kim.
阿金 给他们看看你被剁碎的小鸡鸡
Kim, show them your mangled genitals.
剁碎的小鸡鸡我们就不用看了
We're all set, mangled genitals-wise.
你别乱代表我 我可是很乐意看呢
Speak for yourself, I'd take a peek at them mangled gennies.
或许我们可以算算阿憨欠你多少钱
Uh, perhaps we could put an installment plan in place
然后看看怎么分期付款合适
for the money Han owes you?
他欠您多少钱来着
How much is it, exactly?
女子网球赌输三万吗
On ladies tennis?
这事我们绝对可以解决
I'm sure we can figure this out.
我有张AMC连锁电影院的免费劵
Yeah, I have a free pass to any AMC Theatre.
不过我得先提醒你 此劵不能看IMAX电影
I should warn you, though, it does exclude the IMAX.
阿憨 你自己收着吧
Keep it, Han.
我决定多给你点时间还钱
I've decided to give you a little time to pay me back.
你人真是太赞了
That is so cool of you.
多给多少时间
How much time?
一首歌的时间
Uh, one song.
现在唱
Right now.
对了 阿憨
And Han?
你最好选一首脚打节拍的歌
You better make it a toe-tapper.
因为你唱完之后
'Cause when you're done,
你就要少一根能打节拍的脚趾了
you'll have one less toe to tap.
你不是真要切掉他一根脚趾吧
You're not really gonna take off his toes.
阿金 给他看看你没掉的脚趾
Kim, show him your missing toes.
来吧 阿憨 你的表演时间到了
Come on, Han, it's show time.
应该说 "脚趾时间"到了
I mean, "Toe time."
天啊 这感觉就像是《美国偶像》
Oh, my God, this is like when they make people sing
让那些被淘汰者再唱首歌时一样
on American Idol after they've been voted off.
黄哥 你要多一根脚趾头干嘛
Hwang, what are you gonna do with another toe?
你觉得自己需要多一根
I mean, you think you need another one,
但结果它们只是被束之高阁
and then they just sit on the shelf.
如果我不切掉他的脚趾 那我就会成为
If I don't take his toes, then I'm known as the guy
人们眼中出尔反尔 说切脚趾却不切的人
who says he's gonna take toes and then doesn't take toes.
我能翻阅下点歌本吗
Uh, can I peruse a song book?
可能时间会比较长 因为我非常挑哦
It might take a while, I'm very picky.
阿巴合唱团
Abba...
AC/DC乐队
AC/DC...
阿黛尔
Adele...
我已经帮你选好歌了
I already picked you a song.
唐娜·莎曼的《最后一支舞》
"Last Dance" By Donna Summer.
因为当脚趾头没掉时
'Cause when that toe is gone,
这将会是你最后一次跳舞
it'll be the last time you dance.
快唱
Sing.
♪ 最后一支舞 ♪
♪ Last dance ♪
♪ 爱情最后一支舞 ♪
♪ Last chance for love ♪
♪ 是的 这是我最后的机会 ♪
♪ Yes it's my last chance ♪
♪ 为了今夜的 ♪
♪ For romance ♪
♪ 浪漫 ♪
♪ tonight ♪
♪ 我需要你 ♪
♪ I need you ♪
♪ 在我身边 ♪
♪ by me ♪
♪ 在我身旁 ♪
♪ beside me ♪
♪ 指引我 ♪
♪ to guide me ♪
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
你也听见阿憨唱啦
You heard Han.
他需要我们在他身边 在他身旁 指引他
He needs us by him, beside him, to guide him!
我们是不是该去报警啊
Should we go and get the cops?
不行 等警察来了
No, by the time they get back,
阿憨会少一根脚趾头
Han will have one less toe,
如果黄哥切完住手还好
if Hwang even stops there.
万一他在兴头上 整个脚掌都切了怎么办
What if he takes his whole foot?
阿憨一毫米的高度都矮不起
Han needs all the height he can get.
你之前不是说我们有一笔保底救急金吗
Didn't you say something about us having a money cushion?
我们不能动那笔钱
We can't use the cushion.
那是留给甜点吧运转的 以防一开始生意不好
We need it for the dessert bar in case we have a slow start.
以前我们每一次创业都会出现这种情况
Like we have had with every business we've started before.
你确定吗 因为
You sure? 'Cause...
♪ 求别走 ♪
♪ Don't leave ♪
♪ 求骂我 ♪
♪ scold me ♪
♪ 因为我很坏 ♪
♪ 'cause when I'm bad ♪
♪ 我真的好坏 ♪
♪ I'm so so bad ♪
天平开始向帮他倾斜
Leaning towards helping.
阿憨的确烦人 死宅又不善运动
Han is annoying, nerdy, bad at sports,
但当我们一无所有时 他也给过我们救急金
but he gave us a cushion when we didn't have anything.
麦克斯 我也想帮阿憨
Max, I want to help Han,
但我不想最后搞得我们一无所有
but I also don't want us to wind up with nothing.
历史重演
Again.
让我再看看他的小脸
Let me see him one more time.
♪ 来跳舞吧 ♪
♪ So let's dance ♪
♪ 跳起来 ♪
♪ let's dance ♪
♪ 让我们来 ♪
♪ 跳最后一支舞 ♪
♪ the last dance ♪
我能重唱一遍吗
Can I start over?
我嗓子进空气了
I had a bubble in my throat.
栗宝 我们有重大消息宣布
Chestnut, we have big news.
还有糯米团哦
And something called mochi.
在里面
In here.
我自己进来了
I let myself in.
栗宝居然会说话
Chestnut can talk?
感谢上帝
Thank you, God!
你好呀 可人儿
What's up, good looking?
我至今仍难以置信
I still can't believe
你居然会跟不仅有脸蛋有身材
you're dating someone who looks like that,
还有脑子会读书的男人交往
and can read.
兰迪 你肯定不会相信刚才我们做了什么
Randy, you will not believe what we did.
我们救了阿憨一命
We saved Han's life.
与其说救了他一命 不如说救了他一根脚趾
Well, not his life, so much as his toe,
但我们的善心还是没话说
but still an amazing gesture on our part.
小矮子的故事有一匹布那么长
Long story about a short guy,
但总而言之 我们把餐厅买下了
we bought the diner.
救了他总该有点回报吧
I had to get something out of it.
我又不是无私的特蕾莎修女
I mean, I'm not Mother Teresa.
你们买下了餐厅
You bought the diner?
那家由于法律原因 在谷歌地图上
The diner that doesn't show up on Google Maps
都找不到的餐厅
for legal reasons?
是那家吗
That diner?
你们为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
确切来说 不算买下
Well, not bought, exactly.
我们帮阿憨还债 他给我们部分股权作为交换
We got Han out of debt in exchange for part ownership.
感觉就像 我们花了五年的时间试图逃出地狱
It's like, we spend five years trying to get out of hell,
结果...
and then...
我们买下了地狱
we bought hell!
想不到吧
Crazy, right?
是啊 打死我都想不到
Yeah, no, real crazy.
说到冲动消费 我会想到薄荷糖
When I think of impulse buys, I think of Altoids
或手电筒钥匙扣
or a flashlight keychain.
我该恭喜你们
Well, I guess congratulations.
慢着 你这是什么表情
Wait, what is that look on your face?
我从来没见过
I've never seen it before.
你是生气了吗
Are you mad?
只是意外你都没想过
Just surprised you didn't think
跟我先商量一下
to talk to me about it first.
干嘛啦 我每买一家餐厅都得告诉你吗
What, every time I buy a diner, I have to tell you?
我还有三天就回洛城了
I go back to L.A. in three days.
你连计划一下我们的将来都做不到
You couldn't make a plan for that,
买个餐厅倒是轻而易举
but you bought the diner?
那可是重大的承诺啊
That's a commitment.
现在覆水难收了
Now it's done.
我该去告诉栗宝我们的所作所为了
I should go tell Chestnut what we did.
因为他肯定会笑
'Cause he is gonna laugh.
我知道做什么能弥补
I know what'll make this all okay.
把头埋进咪咪里
Some jug snugs?
埋进你的大咪咪 不是我的
Yours, not mine.
没反应吗
Nothing?
好吧 如果我们不打算玩这个
Well, if we're not gonna do it,
那至少把衣服穿上
at least put on a shirt.
我可是个有冲动的人
I am human.
你真的觉得你会有时间经营我们的感情吗
You really think you're gonna have time for us?
开一家新店 还要当餐厅老板
Starting a new business and owning the diner?
当然有啊
Yes!
我六年级的时候有4份工作
I had four jobs in sixth grade,
我还有时间跟着"破嘴"全国跑
and I still had time to follow Smash Mouth around the country.
不是那个乐队 是我妈很喜欢的一个冰毒贩子
Not the band, a meth head my mom really liked.
栗宝听了这件事 反应也很"大"
Chestnut had a big reaction to the news, as well.
铲屎的铁锹在哪里
Where's the poop shovel?
女老板们 祝贺两位
Hey, boss ladies, congratulations!
我听说现在餐厅是你们的了
I heard that you own the diner now.
所以我今天高兴得抽大麻双烟卷
Which is why I am doing double doobies.
是合伙人
Part! Part owners!
老板还是我
I'm still the boss.
把那玩意放一边去
Put that away!
未"点"待"抽"
Doobie continued.
谁才是老板啊 矮尼·丹扎
Who's the boss, Tiny Danza?
很快又会是我 只要我攒够钱
Well, I will be again, as soon as I scrape up
把钱还给你们
the money to pay you back.
但别担心 从今往后
But don't worry, from now on,
我再也不赌
I'm not gambling on anything
除了打赌请吃墨西哥快餐
but lunch at Chipotle.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
苏菲回归 状态更胜以往
Sophie's back and better than ever!
就像美国的种族歧视
Like racism in America.
我听说了
I heard that.
苏菲 这裙子真是非同凡响
Wow, Sophie, that is some dress.
现在一定有只被扒了皮的豹子 正冻得瑟瑟发抖呢
And there must be one very cold leopard out there.
我喜欢你这身打扮 宝贝
Oh, I like your style, baby.
我意识到
I realized
我不需要穿那些婊气冲天的普通孕妇装
I don't need to wear those basic bitch maternity clothes.
我可以当个非常规孕妇 保留最后那点
I can be maternal without losing that little whisper
告诉人"想操我就来"的风韵
that says, "I'm doable."
没错
Yes, you are.
她还做了一件孕妇物品 供卧室使用
She also made a maternity item for the bedroom.
叫"孕爱神器"
It's called "The Preglige."
奥列格
Hey, Oleg.
去厕所跟我汇"合"
Meet me in the bathroom.
厄尔 我要走了
Hey, Earl, I'm heading out.
之前说好的重演《致命武器》
I guess we'll never get to do that Lethal Weapon reboot
估计是没戏了
we talked about.
没关系 我找阿憨重演《尖峰时刻》好了
That's all right, I'm doing a Rush Hour reboot with Han.
你拿着行李干嘛
What're you doing with that luggage?
我又害你被酒店赶出来了吗
Did I get you kicked out of another hotel?
不 我把机票改签了
No, I changed my ticket.
我今天就回洛杉矶
Going back to L.A. Today.
现在就是今天
But that's today.
这是一张去洛杉矶的机票
And that is a ticket to Los Angeles.
你什么时候想来都行 我等着你
Use it whenever you want and I'll be there.
里面啥也没有啊
This is empty.
对啊 这年头都是网上订票
Yeah, everything's done online now.
我只是做做效果
I just did that for effect.
你会收到一封电邮的
You'll get an email.
祝你的甜点吧和餐厅 一切顺利
Good luck with your dessert bar and the diner.
我还是会去找你的啊
I'm gonna see you.
是啊
Yeah.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
你干嘛一副就此别过 后会无期的样子
Why are you being so good-bye-y?
只要这边事情一定下来 我立刻就去找你
I'm gonna visit as soon as things get settled here.
我们每天都能通电话啊
And we'll talk every day.
我电话做爱比真实做爱更强呢
I'm even better at phone sex than I am at real sex.
我才不信
I find that hard to believe.
这是我简历上唯一没撒谎的技能
It's the only thing on my resume that's not a lie.
我会考虑清楚 我们会想出计划
I'll figure it out. We'll make a plan.
我知道你这么想
I know you think that.
但我觉得一开始我就是对的
But I think I was right the first time.
异地恋行不通
Long-distance relationships don't work.
我觉得我们之间真正的距离是
And I think the real distance between us
我们人生的差距
is where we are in our lives.
什么距离
What distance?
我们现在的距离不到10厘米
I'm three inches away from you.
你还是快回你的餐厅吧
You better get back to your diner.
我爱你 麦克斯
I love you, Max.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
好吧 这下感觉真的像就此别过了
Okay, that felt really good-bye-y.
我没事 厄尔
I'm okay, Earl.
这是给我擦眼泪的
This is for me.
我知道这很难
I know this is really hard,
但你不知道你们的感情会何去何从
but you don't know where this all is gonna end up.
就像你嗑了摇头丸去坐地铁一样
Like you, when you ride the subway on ecstasy.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
恰恰相反 不好
I am the opposite of okay.
作为老板 我可以让你休息一下
You know, as the boss, I could let you take a break.
最多 十分钟吧
I mean, ten minutes, tops.
如果让你休息超过10分钟
If I give you more than ten minutes,
我就会成为人们眼中那个
then I'll be known as the girl who says
出尔反尔 说好给十分钟却没做到的女人
she's gonna give ten minutes, then doesn't give ten minutes.
我想跟店主谈谈
I need to talk to the owner.
我就是
That's me!
这一声答应听得我肝儿疼
Oh, that was really painful.
可能比失去一根脚趾疼多了
And probably worse than losing a toe.